WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.MY-SUBS.com
Your Grace.
The trial will be
getting under way soon.
You got my money?
Later.
Go away.
Grand Maester.
Ser Loras Tyrell.
Are you prepared to stand trial
and profess your guilt or
innocence before the Seven?
There'll be no need for a trial.
I confess before the Seven
and freely admit to my crimes.
To which crimes
will you be confessing?
All of them.
I lay with other men
including the traitor
Renly Baratheon.
I perjured myself
before the gods.
I am guilty of depravity...
dishonesty,
profligacy,
and arrogance.
I see that now.
I humble myself before the Seven
and accept whatever punishment
the gods deem just.
The gods' judgment is fierce,
but also fair.
The Warrior punishes those
who believe themselves
beyond the reach of justice.
But the Mother shows her mercy
to those who kneel before her.
I take full responsibility
for my many sins
and unburden myself
of my desires.
My only remaining wish
is to devote my life to the Seven.
May I be a living example
of their grace
for others to witness.
You understand fully
what this means?
I do.
I will abandon the Tyrell name
and all that goes with it.
I will renounce my lordship
and my claims on Highgarden.
I will never marry
and I will never father children.
Brother Loras...
I ask you to dedicate
your life to the seven gods.
Will you fight to defend your faith
against heretics and apostates?
I will.
No, I can't let them...
Faith is the way, Father.
All right.
I'm ready.
I have to go.
I'm...
I'm late for the trial.
You mutilated him.
You gave me your word.
And I have kept my word.
Once the queen mother's
trial is concluded,
Brother Loras
is free to leave.
And where is
the queen mother?
Her litter never left
the Red Keep.
It appears the queen mother doesn't
wish to attend her own trial.
Go to the Red Keep
and show her the way.
Get the others.
Where's the king?
Elsewhere, I'm afraid.
What's the meaning of this?
I was told that...
Ah.
I have more important
things to do with my time
than waste them
in the presence...
Please, Grand Maester.
I bear you no ill will.
Please forgive me
if you can.
This pains me, my lord.
Whatever your faults,
you do not deserve
to die alone in such
a cold, dark place.
But sometimes before
we can usher in the new,
the old must be
put to rest.
The longer you wait,
the worse it'll be for you.
What are you doing?
There's something wrong.
You have nothing
to fear, Your Grace.
The trial will begin shortly.
Cersei is not here.
Tommen is not here.
Why do you think
they're not here?
If the accused is not here,
she will be tried regardless.
We cannot escape
the justice of the gods...
Forget about the bloody gods and
listen to what I'm telling you.
Cersei understands the
consequences of her absence
and she is absent anyway,
which means she does not intend
to suffer those consequences.
The trial can wait.
We all need to leave.
We all need to leave now.
Loras.
Stay with me.
Let me through.
Get out of my way.
Let us through.
Confess.
- No.
- Confess.
Confess.
It felt good.
Beating me,
starving me,
frightening me,
humiliating me.
You didn't do it because
you cared about my atonement.
You did it because it felt good.
I understand.
I do things because
they feel good.
I drink because it feels good.
I killed my husband because it
felt good to be rid of him.
I fuck my brother because it feels
good to feel him inside me.
I lie about fucking
my brother...
because it feels good to keep our
son safe from hateful hypocrites.
I killed your High Sparrow...
and all his little sparrows...
all his septons, all his septas,
all his filthy soldiers,
because it felt good
to watch them burn.
It felt good to imagine
their shock and their pain.
No thought has ever
given me greater joy.
Even confessing feels good
under the right circumstances.
You've always been quiet.
I said my face would be the last
thing you saw before you died.
Do you remember?
Good.
I'm glad to see your face.
I'm ready to meet the gods.
What?
Now?
Today?
You're not going to die today.
You're not going to die
for quite a while.
Ser Gregor.
This is Ser Gregor Clegane.
He's quiet, too.
Your gods have forsaken you.
This is your god now.
No.
Shame.
I'm very sorry, Your Grace.
Very sorry.
For House Lannister!
Hear me roar!
For House Frey!
We stand together!
May we stand together
through the centuries,
good friends to the last.
And when we drive our swords
through our enemies' hearts,
may we speak the words
of our alliance,
"The Freys and the Lannisters
send their regards."
You don't even have
to do anything, do you?
You just sit there,
a rich slab of beef,
and all the birds
come pecking.
- You're welcome to her.
- She doesn't want me.
She wants your golden
fingers up her twat.
Those two have
their eyes on you.
They have their eyes
on you, cunt.
Not my type.
Not blonde enough?
Ladies, have you met
Ser Bronn of the Blackwater,
hero of the Battle of
Blackwater Bay?
- There you go.
- Maybe I'm not in the mood.
Fuck it.
No need to call me ser just
because I'm an anointed knight.
This came together rather well.
Your father would be pleased.
I'm sure he would be.
Edmure is back in a cell.
Can't go killing my son by law.
It wouldn't be right.
Give the family a bad name.
So the famous Blackfish
killed by foot soldiers, eh?
Legendary warrior,
everyone said.
Have you done much fighting
yourself, Lord Frey?
I'm a bit old for all that.
No, but back in your day.
The purpose of fighting
is defeating
your enemies, isn't it?
I've defeated mine.
Riverrun belonged to House Tully
for a thousand years.
Now it's mine.
What do you call that?
Victory.
Yes, you're a great conqueror.
Go on, mock me, boy.
You think I mind?
The Tullys mocked me
for years.
The Starks mocked me.
Where are they now?
You talk about war
as if you're an expert,
but the one battle
I remember you fighting,
you were captured by Robb Stark,
the Young Wolf.
But it doesn't matter.
Here we are now,
two kingslayers.
We know what it's like to
have them grovel to our faces
and snigger behind our backs.
We don't mind, do we?
Fear is a marvelous thing.
They don't fear the Freys, though.
They fear the Lannisters.
We gave you the Riverlands
to hold the Riverlands.
If we have to ride north
and take them back for you
every time you lose them,
why do we need you?
Show me.
Your Grace,
there's no need...
Show me.
What are your thoughts
concerning the king's funeral?
As the Sept of Baelor
is no longer an option,
perhaps a ceremony
in the throne room?
He should be with
his grandfather,
his brother, his sister.
Burn him
and bury his ashes
where the sept once stood.
Whoa, whoa.
Hello.
From Lord Commander Snow
at Castle Black.
I'm...
I'm to be the new maester.
Oh.
According to our records,
Jeor Mormont is Lord Commander.
He died.
We received no report from
the maester at Castle Black.
Maester Aemon became quite ill
shortly after the election.
He's since passed away.
Which is why I'm here.
This is irregular.
Yes, well, I suppose
that life is irregular.
The archmaester will discuss
these irregularities with you.
In the meantime, you are
permitted to use the library.
Follow me.
No women or children.
When we had feasts,
our family would sit up here...
and I'd sit down there.
Could have been worse,
Jon Snow.
You had a family.
You had feasts.
Aye, you're right.
I was luckier than most.
What is that?
Tell him.
Tell him who it belonged to.
The Princess Shireen.
Tell him what you did to her.
Tell him!
We burned her at the stake.
Why?
The army was trapped.
The horses were dying.
- It was the only way.
- You burned a little girl alive!
I only do what my Lord commands.
If he commands you to burn
children, your Lord is evil.
We are standing here
because of him.
Jon Snow is alive
because the Lord willed it.
I loved that girl
like she was my own.
She was good. She was kind.
And you killed her!
So did her father.
So did her mother.
Her own blood knew
it was the only way.
The only way for what?
They all died anyway.
You told everyone
Stannis was the one.
You had him believing it,
all of them fooled.
- And you lied.
- I didn't lie.
I was wrong.
Aye, you were wrong.
How many died because
you were wrong?
I ask your leave to execute
this woman for murder.
She admits to the crime.
Do you have anything
to say for yourself?
I've been ready
to die for many years.
If the Lord was done with
me, so be it, but he's not.
You've seen the
Night King, Jon Snow.
You know the great war
is still to come.
You know the army of the
dead will be upon us soon.
And you know I can
help you win that war.
Ride south today.
If you return to the North,
I'll have you hanged
as a murderer.
If you ever come back this way,
I will execute you myself.
Mother and the lord's
chamber is prepared for you.
Mother and Father's room?
You should take it.
I'm not a Stark.
You are to me.
You're the Lady of Winterfell.
You deserve it. We're
standing here because of you.
The battle was lost until the
Knights of the Vale rode in.
They came because of you.
You told me Lord Baelish
sold you to the Boltons.
- He did.
- And you trust him?
Only a fool would
trust Littlefinger.
I should have
told you about him,
about the Knights of the Vale.
I'm sorry.
We need to trust each other.
We can't fight a war
amongst ourselves.
We have so many
enemies now.
Jon.
A raven came
from the Citadel.
A white raven.
Winter is here.
Well, Father always
promised, didn't he?
The last time a Tyrell came to Dorne,
he was assassinated.
100 red scorpions, was it?
You have nothing to fear
from us, Lady Olenna.
You murder your own prince,
but you expect me to trust you?
We invited you to Dorne
because we needed your help.
You came to Dorne because
you needed our help.
What is your name again?
Barbaro?
Obara.
Obara. You look like
an angry little boy.
Don't presume to tell me
what I need.
Forgive my sister. What she
lacks in diplomacy, she makes...
Do shut up, dear.
Anything from you?
No? Good.
Let the grown women speak.
The Lannisters have declared
war on House Tyrell.
They have declared war
on Dorne.
We must be allies now
if we wish to survive.
Cersei stole the future from me.
She killed my son.
She killed my grandson.
She killed my granddaughter.
Survival is not
what I'm after now.
You're absolutely right.
I chose the wrong words.
It is not survival I offer.
It is your heart's desire.
And what is my heart's desire?
Vengeance.
Justice.
Fire and blood.
Your ships are nearly ready.
I saw them painting the sails.
I'm curious to see how the
Dothraki do on the poison water.
You're not coming with us.
New strategy?
You want the Second Sons to
attack from the west coast?
If we take Casterly Rock,
the Lannisters will have nowhere to
run when you hit King's Landing.
You're not going to Westeros.
You're staying here
with the Second Sons.
There's finally peace in Meereen.
You will keep the peace while the
people choose their own leaders.
Fuck Meereen.
Fuck the people.
I'm here for you, not them.
You promised me.
"My sword is yours.
My life is yours."
This is what I command.
If I'm going to rule in Westeros,
I'll need to make alliances.
The best way to make
alliances is with marriage.
Who are you marrying this time?
I don't know.
Maybe no one.
But you need to lure all the
noble houses to the table?
Are you a queen or fish bait?
I can't bring a lover to Westeros.
A king wouldn't
think twice about it.
So that's what you want?
To be my mistress?
I'm not proud. I don't care
what perfumed aristocrat
sits beside you
in the throne room.
I don't want a crown.
I want you.
I love you.
And I make you happy.
You know I do.
Bring me with you.
Let me fight for you.
I can't.
The dwarf told you
to do this?
No one tells me
to do anything.
Clever fellow.
Can't argue with his logic.
I'm no use to you over there.
Don't get angry.
I'm not angry.
I'm full of self-pity.
Who comes after you?
Who can ever follow Daenerys
Stormborn, the Mother of Dragons?
A great number
of women, I imagine.
Specific orders
will be left for you
regarding the welfare of Meereen
and the Bay of Dragons.
Bay of Dragons?
We can't call it Slaver's Bay
anymore, can we?
You'll get that throne you
want so badly, I'm sure of it.
I hope it brings you happiness.
I pity the lords of Westeros.
They have no idea
what's coming for them.
Farewell, Daario Naharis.
How did he take it?
No tears.
I know it was hard for you.
You turned away a man
who truly loves you
because he would have been a
liability in the Seven Kingdoms.
That's the kind of self-sacrifice
that makes for a good ruler,
if it's any consolation.
It's not.
No, I suppose not.
I'm terrible at consoling.
Yes, you really are.
All right, how about the fact
that this is actually happening?
You have your armies,
you have your ships,
you have your dragons.
Everything you've ever wanted
since you were old enough
to want anything,
it's all yours for the taking.
Are you afraid?
Good.
You're in the
great game now.
And the great game's terrifying.
The only people who
aren't afraid of failure
are madmen like your father.
Do you know what frightens me?
I said farewell
to a man who loves me.
A man I thought I cared for.
And I felt nothing.
Just impatient
to get on with it.
He wasn't the first
to love you
and he won't be the last.
Well, you have completely
failed to console me.
For what it's worth,
I've been a cynic for as long
as I can remember.
Everyone's always asking me
to believe in things...
family, gods,
kings, myself.
It was often tempting until
I saw where belief got people.
So I said no, thank you to belief.
And yet here I am.
I believe in you.
It's embarrassing, really.
I'd swear you my sword,
but I don't actually
own a sword.
It's your counsel I need.
It's yours.
Now and always.
Good.
I, um...
I had something
made for you.
I'm not sure if it's right.
Tyrion Lannister,
I name you Hand of the Queen.
You're not one
of mine, are you?
No, my lord.
Didn't think so.
Too pretty.
Where are my
damn moron sons?
Black Walder and Lothar
promised to be here by midday.
They're here, my lord.
Well, what are they doing,
trimming their cunt hairs?
Tell them to come here now.
But they're already
here, my lord.
Here, my lord.
They weren't easy to carve.
Especially Black Walder.
What...
My name is Arya Stark.
I want you to know that.
The last thing
you're ever going to see
is a Stark smiling down
at you as you die.
Forgive me, my lady...
if you're at prayer.
I'm done with all that.
I came here every day
when I was a girl.
I prayed to be somewhere else.
Back then I only thought
about what I wanted, never
about what I had.
I was a stupid girl.
You were a child.
What do you want?
I thought you knew
what I wanted.
I was wrong.
No, you weren't.
Every time I'm faced
with a decision,
I close my eyes and see
the same picture.
Whenever I consider
an action, I ask myself
will this action help to make
this picture a reality?
Pull it out of my mind
and into the world?
And I only act if
the answer is yes.
A picture of me
on the Iron Throne...
and you by my side.
It's a pretty picture.
News of this battle will spread
quickly through the Seven Kingdoms.
I've declared for House
Stark for all to hear.
You've declared for other
houses before, Lord Baelish.
It's never stopped you
from serving yourself.
The past is gone for good.
You can sit here
mourning its departure, or...
you can prepare
for the future.
You, my love,
are the future
of House Stark.
Who should the North
rally behind?
A trueborn daughter
of Ned and Catelyn Stark
born here at Winterfell
or a motherless bastard
born in the south?
This is where I leave you.
You're not coming with us?
The Wall is not just
ice and stone.
Ancient spells were carved
into its foundations.
Strong magic
to protect men from
what lies beyond.
And while it stands,
the dead cannot pass.
I cannot pass.
Where will you go?
The great war is coming
and I still fight for the living.
I'll do what I can...
as long as I can.
Thank you, Uncle Benjen.
I wish you both good fortune.
Are you sure
you're ready for this?
I'm the Three-Eyed
Raven now.
I have to be ready for this.
Ned?
Lyanna.
Is that you?
Is that really you?
You're not a dream?
No, I'm not a dream.
I'm here.
Right here.
I've missed you, big brother.
I've missed you, too.
I want to be brave.
Shh.
You are.
I'm not.
I don't want to die.
You're not going to die.
Get her some water.
- No, no water.
- Is there a maester?
Listen to me, Ned.
If Robert
finds out, he'll...
you know he will.
You have to protect him.
Promise me, Ned.
Promise me.
You can't expect
Knights of the Vale
to side with
wildling invaders.
We didn't invade.
We were invited.
Not by me.
The free folk, the northerners,
and the Knights of the Vale
fought bravely,
fought together, and we won.
My father used to say we find our
true friends on the battlefield.
The Boltons are defeated.
The war is over.
Winter has come.
If the maesters are right, it'll be
the coldest one in a thousand years.
We should ride home
and wait out the coming storms.
The war is not over.
And I promise you, friend,
the true enemy
won't wait out the storm.
He brings the storm.
Your son was butchered at the
Red Wedding, Lord Manderly,
but you refused the call.
You swore allegiance
to House Stark, Lord Glover,
but in their hour
of greatest need,
you refused the call.
And you, Lord Cerwyn,
your father was skinned
alive by Ramsay Bolton.
Still you refused the call.
But House Mormont remembers.
The North remembers.
We know no king but the King in
the North whose name is Stark.
I don't care if he's a bastard.
Ned Stark's blood
runs through his veins.
He's my king from this
day until his last day.
Lady Mormont speaks harshly
and truly.
My son died for Robb Stark,
the Young Wolf.
I didn't think we'd find
another king in my lifetime.
I didn't commit my men
to your cause
'cause I didn't want more
Manderlys dying for nothing.
But I was wrong.
Jon Snow avenged
the Red Wedding.
He is the White Wolf.
The King in the North.
I did not fight
beside you on the field
and I will regret that
until my dying day.
A man can only admit
when he was wrong
and ask forgiveness.
There's nothing
to forgive, my lord.
There will be
more fights to come.
House Glover will stand
behind House Stark
as we have for
a thousand years.
And I will stand behind
Jon Snow...
the King in the North!
The King in the North!
Company halt!
Halt!
Come on.
I now proclaim Cersei
of the House Lannister
First of Her Name,
Queen of the Andals
and the First Men,
Protector of the
Seven Kingdoms.
Long may she reign.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.MY-SUBS.com